Guide to the American campaign literature collection, 1954-1978
Department of Special Collections
American campaign literature collection,
1954-1978
Special Collections M0227
1.5 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Restricted access: requires 24 hour paging period.
Provenance
Various sources.
Scope and Content
Collection includes campaign material for the 1960 and 1968 Nixon campaign, 1972 Nixon campaign, and McGovern's 1972 campaign for president.
Also includes miscellaneous material for campaigns other than the presidential race, and misc. earlier campaigns.
Container List
- GOP - NIXON CAMPAIGN 1960, 68
  - Book: Where He Stands - the Life and Convictions of Spiro T. Agnew. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bumper stickers and buttons. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Flyers and newsletters. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Organization Manual - United Citizens for Nixon-Agnew Club. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Pamphlets. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 1, Folder 6)
- GOP - NIXON CAMPAIGN 1972
  - Bumper stickers and buttons. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Flyers and newsletters and news clippings. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Campaign letters. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Pamphlets. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 1, Folder 11)
- DEMOCRATIC PARTY - McGOVERN CAMPAIGN 1972
  - Bumper stickers and buttons. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Flyers and news clippings. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Campaign letters. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Pamphlets and reports. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Democrats in Convention 1972, (booklet) (Box 2, Folder 15a)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 2, Folder 16)
- 1972 ELECTION YEAR
  - General miscellaneous. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Binder - Republican Platform and fact sheets (Volume 3)
  - Oversize - thirteen campaign posters (located in map drawer.) (Box 4)
- EARLIER POLITICAL EPHEMERA
  - On with Roosevelt! Committee. Membership Card. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt for President in 1936 Alameda County.
  - Can labelled Goldwater - the right drink for the conservative taste. -located in Mss. Div. office.
- POLITICAL EPHEMERA 1973
  - 1. Voter's Guide - Palo Alto Municipal Election - May 8, 1973. (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 2. Voter's Pamphlet - P.A. Municipal Election, - May 8, 1973.
  - 3. Campaign Literature - Central Palo Alto Residents' Assoc.
  - 4. News letter - Alan Cranston, U.S. Senator - August 1973.
  - 5. Mimeographed letter - Paul N. McCloskey Jr., Congressman - June 29, 1973.
- 1. Bruére, Robert Walter
  Following the trail of the I.W.W.
- 2. Communist Party of the U.S. National election campaign committee [UNK] speeches 1928
- 3. 1954 Pro American Campaign Kit